springbokcasino.co.za 2014-05-01

# Privacy Policy - SpringBok Casino

##  [ Privacy Policy](http://www.springbokcasino.co.za/privacy-policy)

Springbok Casino is committed to respecting and protecting your privacy. The following statement discloses the information gathered by Springbok Casino.

#### What information do we collect and why?

In order to play for real money at Springbok Casino we need your name, e mail address, mailing address, credit card number and expiration date. This information allows us to process all of your credit requests fast and accurately.

When you enter a competition or promotion at the casino we may ask you for your e mail address, mailing address and name so that we can notify the winners. You can unsubscribe from any mail you do not wish to receive from us.

When you participate in a customer survey we may ask for your name, e mail address and other personal information. We do this to ensure that we construct and modify our casino according to the wishes of our players.

We monitor player traffic patterns and site usage to help us develop and enhance the design of our gaming web sites.

We may use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is used to gather broad demographic information.

#### Advertising System

Our advertising system logs IP addresses to supply more accurate advertising features, such as language specific banners. It does NOT log any e-mail addresses.

#### Account Creation Information

The account information supplied during the account creation process is kept strictly confidential for our own purpose. We do NOT share this information with any third-party company and/or organization.

This information includes customer e-mail addresses and other personal information supplied upon registration. If you supply us with your personal details, the information will only be used for its intended use, such as allowing us to send you cash-out checks and other information which you request.

E-mail Addresses are NOT shared with any other organization for commercial or non-commercial purposes. E-mail addresses will only be used to provide our customers with information regarding new software updates, promotional material, and miscellaneous casino operations, such as deposits and withdrawals.

We collect e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail.

#### Winnings

Your winnings and cash-outs are kept strictly confidential, and winnings information is stored in secure operating environments. Springbok Casino keeps your winnings information private and does not provide this information to any third party unless such information is required to be disclosed by law, regulation or any governmental or competent regulatory authority.

#### Will Springbok Casino sell my information to any third parties?

Springbok Casino will not and does not sell trade or rent any of its players personal information to any parties. Springbok Casino may provide aggregate statistics about our players, sales, Internet traffic, and related site information to a reputable third-party. However, these statistics will include no personally identifying information. Springbok Casino also allows all of its players to opt out of any mails that they do not wish to receive from us. You can do this by [contacting us.](http://www.springbokcasino.co.za/support)
